fiveknuckles.com 2013-05-29

# FiveKnuckles.com Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

• To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

• To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. 

**How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [http://www.fiveknuckles.com](http://www.fiveknuckles.com/)

**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

United States  
info@fiveknuckles.com

**FiveKnuckles.com MMA Betting Advice:**

FiveKnuckles.com and Benjamin Zeidler are not responsible for any decisions made, financial or otherwise, based on information or links provided by FiveKnuckles.com. We advise all viewers to use discretion when viewing our Professional MMA betting Advice page. Please bet within your means only. If you encounter gambling problems of any kind, please contact the gambling help authorities in your area.

It is very important to check the laws and regulation in your own country regarding gambling betting, as it might differ from country to country. We do not promote underage or illegal gambling.

We do not claim to have complete and reliable odds information at the present moment.

Neither Benjamin Zeidler nor anyone associated with FiveKnuckles.com accepts any responsibility whatsoever for any loss that may be sustained as a result of the use (or misuse) of the opinions, odds or advertisements placed at the FiveKnuckles.com website.

FiveKnuckles.com and its contributors do not guarantee winnings and cannot be held liable for losses resulting from the use of information obtained from here. FiveKnuckles.com and its contributors cannot be held responsible for any erroneous or incomplete on-line results. FiveKnuckles.com and its contributors do not accept any responsibility for any erroneous information presented here which can arise due to equipment errors, unforeseeable consequences, acts of God or any other reason whatsoever.

Any questions regarding our disclaimer information, please submit your comments by e-mail to FiveKnuckles.com. Disclaimer information are subject to change at the discretion of FiveKnuckles.com, so please check back regularly. 

**Tracking and Advertising**

Fivknuckles.com knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy covers Fivknuckles.com's treatment of personal information that Fivknuckles.com gathers when you are on the Fivknuckles.com website and when you use Fivknuckles.com services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Fivknuckles.com does not own or control, or to individuals that Fivknuckles.com does not employ or manage. 

**Information Collected by Fivknuckles.com**

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our Fivknuckles.com users:   
1\. Information You Provide to Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.   
2\. Automatic Information:   
o We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Fivknuckles.com and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain "traffic data" on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, Fivknuckles.com cookie information, and the page you requested. Fivknuckles.com uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website.   
o Fivknuckles.com may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed.   
o Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While Fivknuckles.com will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.   

**E-mail Communications**

Fivknuckles.com is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the "Sharing Your Information" section below. Fivknuckles.com may send out e-mails with Fivknuckles.com-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions. 

Cookies 

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. Fivknuckles.com cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is. 

The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use some of Fivknuckles.com's coolest features. 

Fivknuckles.com's advertising partners may place a cookie on your browser that makes it possible to collect anonymous non-personally identifiable information that ad delivery systems use to present more relevant ads. If you would prefer to opt-out of this standard practice, please visit our advertising partner Platform-A's privacy policy and opt-out page. 

**Sharing Your Information**

Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone and that we will share your personal information only as described below. 

Fivknuckles.com Personnel: Fivknuckles.com personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of Fivknuckles.com business. 

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Fivknuckles.com, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred. 

Protection of Fivknuckles.com and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Fivknuckles.com, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

Syndication: Fivknuckles.com allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the Fivknuckles.com website. 

With Your Consent: Except as noted above, we will contact you when your personal information is shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to opt out to prevent the sharing of this information. 

Children Under 18 Years of Age   
You must be 13 years and older to register to use the Fivknuckles.com website. As a result, Fivknuckles.com does not specifically collect information about children. If we learn that Fivknuckles.com has collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask and receive their parents' permission before using Fivknuckles.com or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy   
Fivknuckles.com may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Fivknuckles.com website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed. 

Conditions of Use   
If you decide to visit Fivknuckles.com website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law. 

Effective Date of this Privacy Policy This Privacy Policy is effective as of 02/01/2011.
